Guide to the Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection 1977-2002 MSS 128
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: WNYC-TV "Poetry Spots", 1985-1992
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - An Uncool Yul, 1992 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0205)
      Format: 3/4 in. Umatic SP
    - Poetry Compilation Reel IV, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0206)
    - Poetry Comp IV, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0207)
    - Poetry Spots V - Compliation Reel, 1994 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0208)
    - Poetry Spots V - Compliation Reel, 1994 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0209)
    - Poetry Spots - Various Cuts, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0210)
    - Poetry Spots V; Compilation Air Master, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0211)
    - Poetry Spots V; Compilation Air Master, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0212)
    - Poetry Spots V; Compilation Air Master, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0213)
    - Poetry Spots VI Compilation Reel, 1995 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0214)
    - Poetry Spots Season 6, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0215)
    - Poetry Spots Season 6, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0216)
    - An American Dream; A film by Andrea Kirsch, 1987 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0217A)
    - Treadwinds for Poetry Spots, 1992 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0218)
      Format: 1 in.
    - Counting - Lisa Buscami, Undated (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0219)
    - Chinese Cucumbers - Patricia Smith, Undated (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0220)
    - Poetry Spots III Compilation, Undated (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0221)
    - Poetry Spots V Compilation Uncensored, 1994 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0222)
    - Poetry Spots V; Various Cuts 1-9, 1994 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0223)
    - Poetry Spots Season V Compilation, Undated (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0224)
    - Poetry Spots V Air Master Various 1-9, 1994 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0225)
    - Poetry Spots V Compilation, Undated (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0226)
    - Poetry Spots V - Various Cuts Air Master, 1994 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0227)
    - Poetry Spots VI Compilation Reel, Undated (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0228)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III Tape 1, [1991] (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0229)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III Tape 2, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0230)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III Tape 3, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0231)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III Tape 4, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0232)
    - The Law is in the Seed - Kahnawake Shoot Tape #3, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0233)
    - The Law is in the Seed - Billy Two Rivers #4, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0234)
    - The Law is in the Seed - Final Edit Without Credits, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0235)
    - The Law is in the Seed - Final Edit Dub With Credits, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0236)
    - Poetry Spots - "So How Was Your Day" Tape #1, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0237)
    - Poetry Spots - "So How Was Your Day" Tape #2, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0238)
    - John Ash Poem - Edit Master, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0239)
    - "You Startin' Wif Me"; A Tracie Morris Poem, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0240)
    - "Nostalgia"; Laura Ciporen, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0241)
    - Poetry Spot: "Bacalaitos y Fireworks", 1992 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0242)
    - "A Child's Guide to Parenthood"; Laura Ciporen, [1991] (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0243)
    - Treadwinds, [1994] (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0244)
    - "Just Another Day"; Sandy Esteves, 1992 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0245)
    - Alex Jacobs Outside Interview Tape #2, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0246)
    - "Eternity"; Dave Henderson, Undated (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0247A)
    - "Charlie" - Short Version, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0248)
    - Poetry Spot Opening - Season II Compilation, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0249)
    - Poetry Spots III; Compilation Opening Sequence, 1993 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0250)
    - Poetry Spots III - Padua, Sneed, Blumerzack, Undated (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0251)
    - Poetry Spots Season III - Sample Reel, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0252)
    - Poetry Spots Season 5 - Intro and Credits, Undated (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0253)
    - Poetry Membership Spot With Bob Holman, 1992 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0254)
    - Poetry Rap Reel 2, 1992 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0255)
    - Arlene Gottfried Photos for Lois Griffith Poem, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0256)
    - Dub Photos by Arlene Gottfried, Undated (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0257)
    - Arlene Gottfried Shoot: El Barrio Tape 1, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0258)
    - Arlene Gottfried Shoot: El Barrio Tape 2, 1991 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0259)
    - Poetry Videos - Mark Ameen Tape #12, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0260A)
    - Poetry Videos - Mark Ameen Tape #14, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0261)
    - Video Poetry: Deaf Poets Tape 2A, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0262)
    - Tape #6; Show 104 - PS 61: Classrooms, Tour of School, 1990 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0263)
    - Miguel Pinero Stills - B Tape, Undated (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0264)
    - Nuyorican Poets Café - Rough Cut II, 1990 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0265)
    - Transformations, Undated (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0266)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel Season I, [1990], 1994(Dub date?) (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0267)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel Season II - Part 1, 1991, 1994(Dub date?) (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0268)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel Season II - Part 2, 1991, 1994(Dub date?) (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0269)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel Season III, [1992], 1994(Dub date?) (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0270)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Season IV, 1993, 1994(Dub date?) (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0271)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Season IV - DUB, 1993, 1994(Dub date?) (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0272)
    - Poetry Spots V - Compilation Reel, 1994, 1994(Dub date?) (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0273)
    - Poetry Spots V - Compilation Reel, 1994, 1994(Dub date?) (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0274)
    - Latin Empire - Dub Master B Roll, 1990 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0275)
    - Poetry Spots; Latin Empire - B Roll [Credit] Footage, 1990 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0276)
    - Poetry Spot 5, Undated (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0277)
- Series III: "United States of Poetry", 1996
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - "Lost Planet; USOP; Peter Cook 'Hero Take' ", Undated (Media ID: 128.1014)
      Duration: [00:08:30]
      Original Format: VHS
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - U.S. Of Poetry/AMIC "The Land and the People" Episode #101, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0278)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1 - The Land & The People, [1995] (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0279)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1 - The Land & The People, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0280)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0281)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1 - Rough Cut, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0282)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1 - Images/ Selects, [1995] (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0283)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 2 - A Day in the Life, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0284)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 2 - A Day in the Life, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0285)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 2 - Early, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0286)
    - U.S. Of Poetry/AMIC "The American Dream" Episode #103, 1995 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0287)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3 - The American Dream, [1995] (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0288)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3 - The American Dream, [1995] (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0289)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0290)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3 - The American Dream, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0291)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3 - The American Dream, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0292)
    - U.S. Of Poetry/AMIC "Love and Sex" Episode #104, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0293)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 4 - Love & Sex, [1995] (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0294)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 4 - Love & Sex, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0295)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show #4, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0296)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 4 - Love & Sex, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0297)
    - U.S. Of Poetry/AMIC "The Word" Episode #105, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0298)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 5 - The Word, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0299)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 5 - The Word, [1995] (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0300)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 5 - The Word, 1995 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0301)
    - The United States of Poetry; Shows 1,2,3, [1995] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0302)
    - The United States of Poetry; Shows 1,2,3, [1995] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0303)
    - The United States of Poetry; Shows 4, 5, [1995] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0304)
    - USOP 4 & 5, [1995] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0305)
    - The United States of Poetry: 4) Love and Sex, 5) The Word, [1995] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0306)
    - USOP: Eps. 101 The Land and the People, Eps. 102 A Day in the Life, Eps. 103 The American Dream, [1997] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0307A)
    - United States of Poetry Episode #104 "Love & Sex" Episode #105 "The Word", Undated (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0308)
    - United States of Poetry - Sampler, [1995] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0309)
    - United States of Poetry - Sampler, [1995] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0310)
    - United States of Poetry - Sampler, [1995] (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0311)
    - United States of Poetry; National Market, 1996 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0312)
    - The United States of Poetry; Programs One - Three, 1996 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0313)
    - The United States of Poetry; Programs Four - Five, 1996 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0314)
    - The US of Poetry #27; CR# A76-A79, A81-A82, 1994 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0315)
    - Lost Planet; USOP; Peter Cook "Hero Take", Undated (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0316)
    - Various Poets; United States of Poetry #104 "Love and Sex", 1996 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0317)
- Series IV: Mouth Almighty/ Mercury Records, 1996-1999
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - Ballad of the Skeletons, Undated (Media ID: 128.0990)
      Duration: 00:05:00
    - Maggie Estep "Hey Baby" 2:22 R-rated, Undated (Media ID: 128.0984)
    - Maggie Estep "EPK", Undated (Media ID: 128.0987)
      Duration: 00:06:00
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - SF National Poetry Slam Selects, 1993 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0318)
    - Maggie Estep; "Hey Baby" - Rough Cut, 1994 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0319)
    - [1]--"Hey Baby" Video Mix (Clean) [2]-- "Hey Baby" LP MIX (Clean) [3]-- "Hey Baby" Video Mix (Uncensored), 1994 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0320A)
    - Maggie Estep; "Hey Baby" - R-Rated, [1994] (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0321)
    - Maggie Estep; "Hey Baby" - Version #1 (R-Rated) and Version #3 (G-Rated), [1994] (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0322)
    - Maggie Estep; "EPK", Undated (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0323)
    - Maggie Estep; "EPK", Undated (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0324)
    - Maggie Estep; "EPK", Undated (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0325)
    - The Maggie Estep Combo "EPK/ Arsenio Hall Show", [1994] (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0326)
    - The Maggie Estep Combo "EPK/ Arsenio Hall Show", [1994] (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0327)
    - The Maggie Estep Combo "EPK/ Arsenio Hall Show", [1994] (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0328)
    - Estep/ Arsenio, 1994 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0329)
    - Maggie Estep; Normal Girl on MTV/ Jon Stewart, Undated (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0330)
    - Maggie Estep; "Vicious" Final Cut - Three Versions, 1997 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0331)
    - Maggie Estep; "Vicious" Rough Cut - Three Versions, 1997 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0332)
    - Sekou Sundiata; EPK, 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0333)
    - Sekou Sundiata; EPK, 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0334)
    - Sekou Sundiata; EPK, [1997] (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0335)
    - Last Poets; Rap City, [ca. 1995] (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0336)
    - Our Voices 95-18/Last Poets, 1995 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0337)
    - Last Poets; "Sound FX", 1995 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0338)
    - Last Poets 4/9/97 Edit, 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0339)
    - Beyond Life; Timothy Leary Lives, 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0340)
    - Allen Ginsberg w/ Paul McCartney, Philip Glass & Lenny Kaye; "Ballad of the Skeletons", 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0341)
    - Allen Ginsberg w/ Paul McCartney, Philip Glass & Lenny Kaye; "Ballad of the Skeletons", 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0342)
    - Allen Ginsberg w/ Paul McCartney, Philip Glass & Lenny Kaye; "Ballad of the Skeletons", 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0343)
    - Allen Ginsberg; "Ballad of the Skeletons", Undated (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0344)
    - Allen Ginsberg; "Ballad of the Skeletons", 1996 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0345)
    - Wammo Interview, Undated (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0346)
    - Wammo Footage; Tapes 1 & 2, Undated (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0347)
    - Wammo; "There Is Too Much Light In This Bar", 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0348)
    - Wammo; "Edit"; "There Is Too Much Light In This Bar", 1998 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0349)
    - Mouth Almighty Prod. Presentaion 97, [1997] (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0350)
    - Mercury Records/ Mouth Almighty Presentation, [1997] (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0351)
    - Mouth Almighty 1997 PGD Presentation (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0352)
    - Mouth Almighty PGD Presentation 97, 1997 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0353)
    - Mouth Almighty 8/13/96, 1996 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0354)
- Series V: Grassroots Poetry Videos, 1988-2001
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - "Exchange Place" written by Reggie Gaines, Undated (Media ID: 128.0993)
      Duration: 00:09:00
    - "Psychic Defense" Training for Ex-Lovers, Undated (Media ID: 128.0996)
    - The Poetry Video Learning Project: "Rooms of Our Lives", Undated (Media ID: 128.0999)
      Duration: 00:14:00
    - Doug Knott's Small Dogs Bark 3, Undated (Media ID: 128.1002)
    - "Flying Words Project: 'If You Want It' ", 1989 (Media ID: 128.1017)
      Duration: [00:08:00]
    - "Video Poetry," Curated by George Fifield, June - September 1994 (Media ID: 128.1020)
      Duration: [00:43:00]
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Reggie Gaines; "Exchange Place", Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0355)
    - Reggie Gaines; "Exchange Place", Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0356)
    - "Cab"; R. Gaines, Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0357)
    - "Anavision"; Amy Halloran, 1989 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0358)
    - "Pledge"; Lee Ann Brown, 1990 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0359)
    - Lisa Buscani; "Live at the Green Mill", Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0360)
    - Bob Carroll; [1]-- Four Works [2]-- Impossible Theater "I Buy Shoes", [1]--1981 [2]--1986 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0361)
    - [1]-- Bob Carroll; "Salmon Show" [2]-- KPFA Benefit, Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0362)
    - Dead Bob's Birthday Bash 7/6/88, 1988 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0363)
    - Dead Bob's Birthday Bash 7/6/88, 1988 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0364)
    - Todd Colby Reading Poems, Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0365)
    - Alvin Eng; "Selected Compilation", [1&2]--1990 [3]--1989 [4]--1993 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0366)
    - Pat Smith: Selected Readings, 1990-91, 1991 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0367)
    - Holly Hughes: "World Without End", 1989 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0368)
    - Dean Hacker's Poetry For Bob Holman, Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0369)
    - Larry Goodell: "Colores", 1990 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0370)
    - Vivien Bittencourt/ Vincent Katz - April Dark Rain 1987 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0371)
    - Two Of Kenneth Koch's "One Thousand Avante-Garde Plays", 1990 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0372)
    - Flying Words Project: "If You Want It", 1989 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0373)
    - Fanny Howe: "Light Words To Rumi Over Time", Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0374)
    - Fanny Howe: "Be Again", Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0375)
    - Fanny Howe & John Gianvito: "What Nobody Saw", Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0376)
    - Elmer Lang, Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0377)
    - Deacon Lunchbox 2/20/91, 1991 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0378)
    - "Eileen Myles for President", 1992 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0379)
    - Lisa Siegel & Kendrick Jarret: "Bicycle Days", Undated (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0380)
    - Art Performance, 1989 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0381A)
    - PBS Innovations Series: The Future Is Now - Eliot Soloway Segment, 1992 (Aired) (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0382)
    - Poet Laundromat, 1988 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0383)
    - Mexico City Blues: A Reading With Live Music, 1988 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0384)
    - Future of Poetry Party at Electronic Café International, 6/30/19?? (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0385)
    - Elec. Cafe, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0386)
    - "Words Against War"; San Francisco, 1/15/91, 1991 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0387A)
    - Bad Words: 8 Excerpts, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0388)
    - Zero-TV, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0389)
    - Best of RSPT Live, 1990 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0390)
    - Quick Cuts, 1989 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0391)
    - [1]-- Before the War [2]-- California One, 1990 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0392)
    - Dennis Moritz: "Something To Hold On To…", Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0393)
    - Neill Bogan: "The Dead Could Not Afford Heaven", [1991] (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0394)
    - "The Dead Could Not Afford Heaven" Part One, 1991 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0395)
    - Alive From Off Center; Press Preview 1990 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0396)
    - Lord Buckley, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0397)
    - Eight Million: Child & Mori, 1991 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0398)
    - History & Memory for Akiko Takashige, 1991 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0399)
    - Elizabeth Streb / Ringside - Promo Video, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0400)
    - Basil King / Dave Geary, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0401)
    - "Corporation With a Movie Camera", 1992 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0402)
    - Dreams Inside and Out, 1982-1989 (Filmed) (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0403A)
    - Behind Every Great Man Is A Thin Boy Waiting To Get Out, 1991 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0404)
    - Night of the Living Sidemen, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0405A)
    - Psychic Defense Training For Ex Lovers, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0406A)
    - Psychic Defense Training For Ex Lovers, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0407)
    - Hopatcong Arrival, 1993 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0408)
    - Jim Cohn: [1]--"Prarie Falcon" [2]-- "Atonement", Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0409)
    - "Rooms of Our Own" - Three Shows, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0410)
    - Poetry Vignettes - Bob Borgatti/ Paul Lamont, Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0411)
    - Vintage Swat's Big Horror Poetry Series 1987-90, 1987-1990 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0412)
    - "From The Fringe": a poetry spot by Mickey Z, 1993 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0413)
    - Dana Gioia Poetry Reading, 1993 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0414)
    - Brooke Berman - Three Text Video(s), Undated (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0415)
    - Consumer Response, 1991 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0416)
    - Urban Ritual, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0417)
    - [1]-- Candlelight [2]-- Land/Scape [3]-- Wings of Fire, [1]--1993 [2,3]--1992 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0418A)
    - Downset Surroundings, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0419A)
    - Wayne Lammers 5 Music Videos, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0420A)
    - Manifest Arts Poetry Video Series, 1990 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0421)
    - A Poet In The House, 1993 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0422)
    - 3 Poetry Slams at the Croc, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0423)
    - CNN Poetry Slam Segment, 1993 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0424)
    - Rise & Shine Productions/ The Dome Project Presents: For The Ed, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0425)
    - The Poetry Video Learning Project: "Rooms of our Lives", 1986 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0426)
    - Lonnie Shesher: [1]-- Cherokee Landing 1987 [2]-- S/Ding Central Hall 1986, [1]--1987 [2]--1986 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0427A)
    - Gwen Gosé: "Short Shorts & Bell Bottom Bikinis" (Excerpts), 1994 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0428)
    - Doug Knott's Small Dogs Bark 3, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0429A)
    - Doug Knott's Small Dogs Bark 3, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0430A)
    - Laurel Ann Bogen: "Wings/ That Which Takes Fight, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0431A)
    - Toby Vann: [1]-- Continuum [2]-- Reservoir, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0432)
    - Wayne Lammers, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0433)
    - Ray McNiece - Promo Tape, 1994 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0434A)
    - Jean Howard: [1]-- Women Without Children [2]-- The Light, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0435)
    - Spoken War, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0436A)
    - Manuel Perez-Tejada: [1]-- The Morphing Poets [2]-- Walls of Haze [3]-- The Rituals of the Wind, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0437)
    - tomandandy: Sound Image Reel, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0438)
    - Rick Shapiro: Conan & Ceasar Salad, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0439)
    - Mike McCallister: "Skinny Boys", 1994 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0440)
    - Ellyn Maybe, Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0441)
    - Raymond Bally: "Outsider IBN", Undated (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0442)
    - Reno Roast, 1994 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0443)
    - Michael McAllister: "Lift", Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0444)
    - Michael McAllister: "That Night", 1994 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0445A)
    - Edwin Torres in Berlin, [1994] (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0446)
    - Edwin Only, [1994] (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0447)
    - Willie Perdomo & Mike Tyler in Berlin, [1994] (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0448)
    - 67985 #3, [1994] (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0449)
    - [1]-- Willie Perdomo, Edwin Torres, Mike Tyler in Berlin 9/94 [2]-- Radio Fritz Interview, 1994 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0450)
    - V. Katz: "Polyergus", 1993 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0451)
    - Billy Lamont, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0452)
    - Billy Lamont, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0453)
    - Katie Soljak, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0454)
    - #1 - Robert Mitchell, 1996 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0455)
    - Jeff McDaniel: "Check the Bags", Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0456A)
    - The Badger: Down With Jeff, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0457)
    - Laurel Ann Bogen: "Wings/ That Which Takes Fight", Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0458)
    - The Psychic Poets Show, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0459)
    - Wanted: X-Cheerleaders, 1994 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0460)
    - Cosmic Rap, 1997 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0461)
    - Video Graf 1, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0462)
    - Lynne [Beyer] Memorial, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0463)
    - Him, Them, Her, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0464)
    - Kathe Burkhart: Performance Pescara Italy, 1995 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0465)
    - Talking Headz, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0466)
    - The Minneapolis Poetry All-Stars, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0467)
    - Kei Kunihiro Poetry Reading, Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0468)
    - Andy Biskin: "The Big Flea", Undated (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0469)
    - Video Poetry, 1994 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0470)
    - Lydia Lunch: "The Gun is Loaded", Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0471)
    - Video/ Poetry work by Kurt Heintz, Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0472)
    - Jean Howard: [1]-- Women Without Children [2]-- The Light, Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0473)
    - Nazi Youth in Brugge, 1997(Dub) (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0474)
    - Via Delle Cascine, Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0475)
    - Poetry Video: Larry Winfield, [1990, 1992] (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0476)
    - Richard Loranger: [1]-- "TCS" [2]-- "in corpus flagranter", [1]--1997 [2]--1996 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0477)
    - The Knitting Factory: The Last Poets, [1996] (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0478A)
    - Cross Talk, [1996] (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0479)
    - Michel Negroponte: "No Accident", Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0480)
    - "Big": Tribe Magazine, Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0481)
    - The Bitter Poet - Solo, 1996 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0482)
    - Highlights from The Bitter Poet Show, [1996] (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0483)
    - Christian Vetz, Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0484)